All across the country
right now, as you know,
states are trying their best
to handle the coronavirus,
and they're doing it
in different ways.
And New York has taken
social distancing so seriously
that Mayor Bill de Blasio
has now announced
that he's gonna start ripping
down basketball hoops
out of all the city parks
so that people don't want
to go and play there.
Oh, and, fun fact, de Blasio
is the only mayor in America
who has to bend down
when he rips out the hoops.
Oh!
So, that's what's happening
in New York.
But other states
are taking a different approach
to keep themselves safe,
uh, hanging up
a "no trespassing" sign.
REPORTER: Fly to Florida
and it will really cost you.
You're going to have
to self-isolate for two weeks
before do you anything else.
Hopefully, that will be
a deterrent for people.
If you're just simply trying
to escape here,
uh, to avoid the restrictions
that have been put in place
in your own state, that is
probably not a good idea.
Meantime, both Alaska and Hawaii
are now requiring
mandatory 14-day quarantines for
everyone entering their states.
REPORTER 2: They say
if you aren't able to comply
with the quarantine,
you will need
to postpone your trip.
I hope that everyone complies
and visitors do not come here.
We do want those who may have
scheduled trips to the islands--
take the action to cancel
or reschedule their trip.
Yeah, that's right.
If you try and get off the plane
in Alaska,
Hawaii, or Florida,
instead of a guy with a sign
holding up your name
at the airport,
people just have a sign
that says,
"Turn around, dick."
And, I mean, I'm assuming
your name is Dick.
I mean, they could write
"Richard," if you prefer that.
They just-- "Turn around"
and the person.
But if these states really want
to keep people out,
instead of tourism ads,
you know what they need?
They need to make
some anti-tourism ads.
In fact,
we did it for them.
ANNOUNCER:
Ah, Hawaii.
With its sandy beaches,
lush rainforests,
and friendly people,
Hawaii is heaven on earth,
or at least it was
until you dirty mainlanders
came and infected us.
From now on,
just stay the hell away.
Remember,
we've also got volcanoes,
and we're not afraid
to throw you into one.
Hawaii.
Go to Florida. It's closer.
ANNOUNCER 2: Are you looking
for breathtaking landscapes,
untamed wildlife,
and blissful solitude?
Well, tough shit.
We don't want you here.
And your tropical ass
wouldn't last a day anyway.
This is Alaska, mother(bleep).
We're basically in Russia.
We still use dogs for cars.
Alaska. Come one step closer
and I swear to God
we'll blow up all the oil.
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER 3:
Can't wait to visit Florida?
Sure, you can.
It's not all sunshine
and Mickey Mouse down here.
-Remember that guy
on bath salts -Bath salts.
who tried to eat
another guy's face?
That happened here.
And you know where
all those Florida men live?
In (bleep) Florida.
Plus, this is where
all the old people are.
Does this look
like a party to you?
You really need
a list of reasons to stay away?
Fine. Angry gators,
frozen iguanas, Mar-a-Lago,
humidity, stand-your-ground,
hurricanes, Tim Tebow.
Florida.
Stay away
from our penis-shaped hellhole.
♪ ♪